So hello everyone welcome back to our channel
Stocks for Wealth so friends in this
video we will discuss
about ACI Lombard General Insurance Company's quarter two financial results
let's see how the results have been
and what were the market
estimates we will also check that and will
also analyze it in the chart so the video is going to be
very important
watch the whole so first of all let's talk
on the sales front if we look at the sales
last year which were 5271 crores and the
same has increased by 17% this time it has come to
6147 crores in this quarter which is also
seen increasing by 5600 if seen from the previous quarter if we
talk about the net profit front then where the net profit
was 577 crores last year it has jumped by 20%
this time their profit has come to 694
crores if seen from the previous quarter
EPS has increased from 580 to 694
this time  It has come to ₹ 100 crores. If we talk about the TA front, then
here you can see that TA has
jumped to ₹ 23 crores,
increasing from ₹ 62 crores to ₹ 940 crores. It is
also seen increasing from the previous quarter.
So whether we talk about quarter-on-quarter basis
or year-on-year basis, a
good improvement is being seen in the results. The
results of quarter two are looking explosive. Now
let us also look at some important points.
Apart from this, let us
also check what were the market estimates.
An important update for this company, which has
also come out in the board meeting, is that this
company has declared an interim dividend,
that too at 5.5 per equity share, which if
seen on percentage face value, is
seen at almost 55 per share. So,
this time the company has also provided a decent dividend
and the record date for this has been
kept as 28th of
October, that is, if these shares are present in your demat account
from 28th October.  If you
buy it before 27th October, then
you will definitely become eligible for it and
when will this antim dividend be paid, it will be
paid to you on 16th November, you can see here,
before 16th of November, this
dividend will be paid to you before that
or by that date, so friends, I
want to tell you one thing, if you are looking to buy any
stock after seeing the dividend or bonus split,
then do
not do this at all, okay, invest only after looking at the business model of the company and after
looking at the features, let's
see on the chart, how is it
looking, so friends, we have
opened the chart of this stock on daily time, if we
talk about the performance of the last one year, then you
can see here that a
great rally has been seen in the last one
year, the investors have
increased the money of their investors by almost 50% and if seen in the current time, a
decline has been seen in the stock while creating a double top and that
correction which was its support level was 2100
Breaking that too, finally a
closing was seen around 2020 in the last session
and my view on this from the educational point of view is that
here the
stock is seen sustaining around 200 2020
because
if seen, there is a next
support level here and here the stock may
see a good movement if the market opens in tomorrow's trading session i.e. on Monday
and the stock may
touch the level of 2100 while opening at 2100. This is possible, there is
no guarantee that this will happen.
Nothing is guaranteed in the stock market,
so do any work at your own risk. If
you take any investment or decision because of my advice, it is
not that it will happen. I
am not God, so you
can definitely keep an eye on it. If it sustains above this
and if the daily time frame gives a closing above 2100, then
definitely you should make a new entry in it.  You
can and by chance if it breaks this level, it does,
although the results are
quite good, it is possible that
you may get to see levels up to 1900, it is not going to break below this at
this time at all if there is
no negative sentiment in the market,
so friends, keep an eye on it,
otherwise how did you like the initiative of this video, then
please
like the video, subscribe to the channel and turn on the bell
icon so that
you can get the notifications of the video first, till then we will
meet with a new video
in the next video, thank you for watching.